[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
[In my prime]
[Episode 7]
Thank you, sweetie.
Dad.
The golden toads at Cao Xin's house
were all bought from you.
It's been over ten years.
I'm very magnanimous.
The past
is in the past.
Doesn't Uncle Cao
think the same way?
But
then again...
Fortunately, I was laid off early,
and your mom had the foresight
to start this small business early
and get a head start.
Look at the people being laid off now.
It's hard for them to take our place.
So,
people should be content.
Dad.
When I get into Beining University
and become a big boss after graduation,
you can work for me.
I'll make sure you never get laid off.
You really are my sweet girl,
so warm and caring.
But,
about Uncle Cao
buying this golden toad,
you must not tell your mom.
Got it?
Don't worry.
Come sit up front.
Okay.
I will take you
for a ride in a convertible.
Let's go!
Sit tight.
Slow down.
You are really something.
No wonder the pointer
on the electricity meter
keeps spinning.
You have too much energy to burn,
don't you?
Fine,
then get to work.
If you don't finish
shelling these peanuts today,
don't even think about sleeping.
No matter how big the mistake is,
you still have to let the kid eat.
Shut up.
I'm disciplining the kid.
Don't interrupt me.
It's always like this.
I pull on one side,
and you pull on the other.
Are you playing tug-of-war with me?
She doesn't sleep at night,
just sitting around
coming up with wicked ideas.
Doesn't she have energy to spare?
Then let her do some chores.
Doing chores is good.
It's a good way to exercise.
Didn't the teacher say
the college entrance exam
is not just about brainpower,
but also physical fitness?
Just eat your food.
She's full of bad ideas.
I don't know who this kid takes after.
If you leave, I won't see you off.
If you come,
no matter how heavy the wind and rain are,
I will go pick you up.
Writing a love letter?
No.
Practicing handwriting.
Who are you trying to fool?
Practicing handwriting on pink stationery?
Come, let me see.
No.
Let me see.
Guys,
Qi Zhi wrote a love letter.
Come and see!
Xin,
come here.
take this chicken soup over
to the house across the street.
Qi Zhi isn't home today.
No one will drink it.
Qi Zhi isn't here, but Qi Ni is.
Grandpa, listen to me.
She and her mom are on the same side.
She won't drink your chicken soup.
I'm telling you,
she will definitely drink it.
Here,
take it.
Damn Cao Xin.
At least you have a conscience.
Where did you go?
What was that noise outside?
Was someone
rattling our iron gate?
No.
A cat.
I don't know whose cat it was,
but I chased it away.
Are you really that obedient?
Our daughter hasn't eaten all night.
Didn't you even think
about sneaking her some food?
Honey, what are you talking about?
Am I that kind of person?
I firmly follow
and uphold your decisions.
You're right.
This girl is too naughty
and needs a lesson.
I think
you did absolutely nothing wrong.
I thought you had some backbone.
But when you were starving,
you still drank my chicken soup.
It's called returning a favor.
Don't you get it?
That bunch of golden toads at your house
was bought from us too.
I was wondering where
those ugly toads
came from.
Turns out
they crawled in from your house.
I thought my dad's taste
wouldn't be so bad as to buy that.
So he was secretly
supporting your business.
Stop.
You don't have to be so mean.
No one forced your family to buy them.
Your dad did it willingly.
Then are you drinking this chicken soup
of your own free will?
Don't let my mom know.
You mean buying the toads
or drinking the chicken soup?
Figure it out yourself.
Hurry up.
Stop rushing me.
Dad.
Drink it all?
Yes.
Come on, drink it quickly.
I just heated it up for you.
Finish it.
Then go do two sets of exercises
right away.
Dad.
Did you buy
all these things from
Uncle Qi?
Who told you that?
Is that true?
Your Uncle Qi's family
is having a hard time.
It doesn't matter who we buy from.
Helping others is helping ourselves.
We are all neighbors.
Right?
Come.
About this,
don't tell Mrs. Huo.
No.
What exactly happened to Mrs. Huo?
Why is everyone keeping it a secret?
Class 1, come in.
Talent.
That's talent.
Quiet down, everyone.
I have something to tell you.
The school sports meet
is about to start.
I know everyone
has been
under a lot of study pressure lately.
But the sports meet
is not just a test
of individual ability;
it also represents class honor.
So I hope everyone can
participate actively.
Those who placed last year,
I've already
signed you up.
This year, we must
win first place as a team.
We can't let Class 2 take it again.
Monitor.
Does that mean
we don't have to sign up
if we have no special skills?
All events
must have participants.
How about this?
If any event needs someone,
you'll fill in.
Stop messing around.
With my small build,
don't you know?
I'd better just
be a cheerleader
and cheer for our classmates.
Go! Go! Go!
Why can't you compete?
If it were a long-face competition,
you'd definitely come first in the grade.
You talk too much.
Shot put or medicine ball?
[Qi Shi]
What's going on?
For the women's 4x200 relay,
why is Qi Shi the only one signed up?
No one wants to run with Qi Shi.
They say it's a waste of time.
We'll definitely lose anyway.
Then what should we do?
Our class doesn't have enough people.
We have to forfeit.
Why don't you go talk to Qi Shi
and tell her not to run?
With her physical condition,
there's no point in running.
It would only cause trouble for our class.
I'll go find her.
Are you playing soccer later?
[Qing Wu First Senior High School]
Here's the situation.
I asked
the other classmates.
Everyone thinks
your physical condition
might not be suitable for the competition.
Look,
for the 4x200m relay,
if you sign up alone,
you can't participate.
How about...
Cao Xin,
tell me,
do you ever feel
like there can only be one winner?
Setting aside our families' relationship,
I admit you're excellent
and have good grades.
But when it comes to grades,
either you come first
or I do.
We're neck and neck.
As for handling things,
you're steady, and I'm flexible.
But every year
for the class monitor election,
I never get elected.
Where do you think I fall short?
Don't overthink it.
They're just talking nonsense.
Since I was little,
they called me "White-Haired Girl"
and called me a monster.
I refused to accept it,
so I fought them.
After that,
they didn't dare bully me anymore.
I thought
I'd become like everyone else.
But I hadn't.
I hadn't become like everyone else.
But later on,
everyone began to
overprotect me
and show me excessive sympathy.
During group cleanups,
they gave me the easiest jobs.
They wouldn't let me take PE.
I know
they mean well.
But the more they
tiptoed around me
and avoided mentioning my illnes
for fear of hurting me,
the more I felt
that it was just another way
of reminding me
that I was different from everyone else.
Running for class monitor
and joining the sports meet,
I only wanted to prove
that I was just like everyone else.
I'm not a sore loser.
I don't care
whether I was elected
or whether anyone
wanted to run with me.
I just wanted a chance,
a fair chance to compete.
Even if I lost,
I wanted to lose fair and square.
Cao,
come down and play football.
Hurry up. The game is about to start.
What a shame.
I don't mean you.
I mean Qi Shi.
Even though she's so competitive,
she's actually had it tough.
Don't be mad at me for saying this.
If Qi Shi were the class monitor,
she might not be worse than you.
No matter how capable she is
or how many first places she gets,
the teachers always say,
"It's a pity she has this illness."
Speech contests,
pep rallies,
all the chances to stand out
have been handed to you, haven't they?
Take yourself, for example.
You two are neighbors
who grew up together.
Whenever she beats you,
haven't you thought
that, in the competition between you two,
she's always just an outsider?
No matter how capable she is,
she's never really taken seriously.
Tianji!
Over there!
Nice shot!
Nice shot! Nice shot!
Go play goalie!
Shoot!
Attack!
Are you okay?
Cao Xin,
can you keep playing?
Do you want to rest for a while?
No, no.
Come on.
Are you sure you can do this?
Zhi.
Did you run all the way back
from the provincial sports school again?
How did you know it was me?
I could smell your sweat
from far away.
I brought you chocolate,
and you still complain about me.
My bad, my bad, my bad.
Zhi,
can I discuss something with you?
Can you teach me how to run?
Why would you want to
run with your condition?
If Mom finds out,
she'll scold me to death.
Whatever.
Forget it if you won't teach me.
No.
Why are you so impulsive?
Pick something else.
Let's talk about it. Pick something else.
Anything is fine.
Pass it quickly. Over there!
Time's up!
That wasn't easy.
I'm exhausted.
I didn't expect us to tie.
We went easy on you. Couldn't you tell?
Your goalie is injured.
We just didn't feel like playing you.
A tie is a tie.
Stop pretending.
Who are you saying is pretending?
You really don't know
what's good for you, do you?
I'm saying you are.
Who are you talking about?
Enough, enough.
I'm saying you are.
Who are you saying is pretending?
Enough, enough, enough.
Is your foot okay?
Let me push the bike for you.
I'm thinking about what Qi Shi just said.
For so many years,
I've never beaten her.
The only thing I have over her
is
being an ordinary person.
Why are you being so profound?
I don't quite get it.
I think
you're just under too much pressure.
How about
I take you somewhere to relax
and blow off some steam?
Want to go to an
Internet cafe?
You can choose from
all kinds of online games.
That latest game,
I'm really good at it.
I'm not afraid of
playing one-on-one or in a group.
Do more practice questions.
Otherwise, your mom will beat you again
after the next exam.
Cao Xin, you're back.
What do you want to do?
Are you trying to snitch on me?
Some other time. My mom's not home.
Qi Shi.
Let's compete fairly, just once.
You're not staying home on the weekend?
Where are you going?
I'm... going to school.
To school?
Mrs. Huo.
Let's go.
Go ahead.
Come back early.
I'm leaving, Mrs. Huo.
Where are you going?
Can't any of you stay at home?
It's the weekend,
and you're all running out.
You're going out
in white sneakers?
If you go out,
they'll get ruined.
Wash them yourself
when you get back.
I'll wash them myself, Mom.
I'm going out for a walk.
Get back in the house.
Don't idle around all day.
Wash all the clothes
you brought back
yourself.
I'll wash them when I get back.
Dad, I'm heading out.
Close the door.
Is walking around in broad daylight
your idea of fair competition?
What if I say yes?
Do you dare to listen to me today?
Of course I dare.
Have I ever been afraid of you?
All right.
Aren't you going to participate
in the sports meet race?
I'll teach you.
I've thought about it.
Your eyesight isn't very good,
but running is like doing math problems.
Practice makes perfect.
The track is only so wide.
If you run enough,
your feet will naturally know the way.
To be absolutely safe,
I'll be on the sidelines
calling your name.
Run toward
my voice.
You'll be fine.
But this is a relay race after all.
If we don't have enough people,
we still can't compete.
Bring her one week of free lunches.
Do her classroom-cleaning duty for a week.
And
do a week's worth of math homework for her.
I've really pulled out all the stops.
Thanks.
Are you satisfied with
my organizational skills as class monitor?
Very satisfied.
That's why you're the class monitor.
Let's go.
I'll show you the track.
Isn't this just messing around?
With Qi Shi's condition,
how can she train for running?
What's wrong?
I think compared to superficial injuries,
making her happy
is the most important thing.
Makes sense.
Right?
What's Cao Xin
teaching her?
Qi Shi's running posture
looks terrible.
Who are you saying is a bad teacher?
He's teaching her quite well.
No.
If she's going to train,
she needs to do it properly.
Otherwise, she could get hurt more easily.
Isn't she practicing properly?
Let's go.
Qi Shi!
Zhi.
Why are you here?
I asked Qi Zhi to come and help.
I have to say.
You have a
future Olympic champion right here,
but you asked an amateur to teach you.
Isn't that a waste of talent?
You refused
to teach me before.
Qi Shi,
I brought you sunscreen.
You can use it when the sun is strong.
Maybe it'll be cloudy that day,
and you won't need it.
What's wrong, Zhi?
Nothing.
Even if it's cloudy,
UV rays are still strong,
so you need sunscreen,
right?
And hats and stuff,
make sure you wear them.
But seriously,
I'm worried about your health.
If it gets to be too much,
tell me right away.
Don't push yourself.
Maybe you should sit this one out.
Zhi,
I haven't even started yet.
Come on, look at me. Lift your right leg.
Hold this leg with both hands,
and bring your thigh as close
to your chest as possible.
At the same time, relax this foot.
Step forward.
Right.
Pay attention to this foot.
Don't flex or point it.
You must relax it.
Okay?
Come on.
Come on, relax.
Right, hold it. Stand firm.
Relax this foot. Don't tense up.
Relax. Relax.
Right, step forward.
Okay.
Good.
That's enough.
Don't be too perfect,
or my sister will get jealous.
Relax.
Make sure the foot underneath
stays relaxed.
Okay?
Now, pay attention to this movement.
Don't let your knees go past your toes.
Try to keep your weight on the right side.
Then shift from this side
to the other side.
Then face forward.
Face forward.
Right, turn to the front.
You need to do both sides.
Both sides are fine.
Turn to the front.
You two need to
swing your inner arms in sync.
The rhythm must be exactly the same.
Because you are going to
be her guide runner.
Your rope is a guide rope,
what keeps you together.
At the start,
hold hands first
so you can find
a shared rhythm.
Right, move with your bodies.
Find a shared rhythm.
Come, give me your left hand.
Right, your right hand.
Adjust it
to a length
that feels comfortable for both of you.
Okay.
Right.
Guide her hand,
hold her wrist,
and place it on the starting line.
Place it properly first.
Right, place it on the starting line.
Place it properly.
Okay.
When I say "Set,"
raise up and get ready to run.
Come on, lift your hips.
Lift your hips.
A little higher.
Right.
Don't look at the ground. Look ahead.
Come on, let's try it.
Set.
Okay, come back. Let's do it again.
Ready.
On your marks.
♪ When the world falls still ♪
Cao Xin,
♪ There is nothing left to argue ♪
on the track,
you are her eyes
♪ I stand at the crossroads ♪
and her crutch.
You are her only support
on the track.
♪ While memories flood the station ♪
You not only have to tell her
the track conditions
and ensure her safety,
♪ How do you keep living ♪
but also, based on her stride
and rhythm,
adjust your own frequency
♪ When every hope has come apart ♪
to become her only support.
Okay?
Go, Class 1, Grade 11!
[The 23rd Athletic Meet of Qingwu First High School]
♪ You stumble through the years ♪
♪ You give what you can, then wait ♪
♪ After all, who hasn't known ♪
♪ The kind of sorrow words cannot hold? ♪
♪ Through the shadows, through the heat ♪
♪ What is there left to fight ♪
On the field,
you are her eyes.
♪ Why does this world ♪
♪ Make me, this time ♪
This end of the rope
is your medal of honor.
That end
is her dream.
♪ Finally see myself ♪
♪ Still, I will love; still, I may lose ♪
♪ Still, I will not look back ♪
♪ Looking foolish in the light ♪
♪ I will choose to be the exception ♪
♪ No matter how slight the chance ♪
I am just a camellia
♪ I will reach for it ♪
of a different color.
♪ Because this life of mine ♪
I will definitely
bloom as freely
♪ Is meant for something brighter ♪
as the other flowers.
♪ Still, I will love; still, I may lose ♪
♪ Still, I will not look back ♪
♪ Even if it was never written in the stars ♪
♪ I will keep fighting ♪
♪ And start again ♪
Qi Shi passed someone!
Come on! Come on! Come on!
♪ For even in the darkest night ♪
♪ There is ♪
♪ A glimmer of light, shining because of me ♪
Come on, Qi Shi!
Come on! Come on! Come on!
Team doctor!
Why did she fall?
Qi Shi! Qi Shi, are you okay?
Are you okay, Qi Shi?
Are you okay? Are you okay?
Come on! Come on! Come on!
Are you okay?
Can you hold on?
Qi Shi, are you okay?
Qi Shi, are you okay? Qi Shi?
Come on, Qi Shi!
Come on, Class 1, Grade 11!
Come on! Come on! Come on!
Come on, chubby girl!
Come on!
Are you okay?
Come on! Come on! Come on!
Even though our class got fourth place,
I finished the race
and won the Sports Star award.
It's already amazing
that you finished the race
while injured.
Qi Shi,
you boosted our morale
with your strong will.
We stood out more than the first place.
Cao Xin.
Thank you.
For what?
Thank you for not treating me
differently.
I wouldn't dare underestimate you.
But you should be careful too.
No matter where we are,
I won't go easy on you.
Fine.
Just don't let it happen that
I get into Beining and you don't.
Then you won't even have a chance
to compete with me.
After all,
your performance in exams is inconsistent.
What's wrong with you?
Have you forgotten who helped you today?
Without me, you couldn't even
find the track.
And you still mock me.
Who's mocking you?
I'm only reminding you.
Don't be ungrateful.
Can you honestly say your performance
hasn't been inconsistent over the years?
Get off.
Fine, I'll get off.
So what if you have a bike?
No wonder Mom said
you people in the Cao family
turn your backs on people.
I wouldn't dare
accept a favor from the Cao family.
Qi Shi!
It's just a school sports meet,
not the Olympics.
Why are you pushing yourself so hard?
I wasn't.
If you weren't,
how did you end up like this?
You're as stubborn as a mule.
Don't you know
your own physical condition?
You haven't even brushed
the mud off your pant legs,
yet you want to reach for the stars.
For a school sports meet,
you could have
just gone through the motions.
Why did you have to try so hard?
Did trying so hard do any good?
You still lost.
You're not allowed to go next time.
I promise I won't go.
You promise it every time,
but every time, you
find some new way to get into trouble.
If you dare use the door bar
as a golden cudgel again,
you'll be sorry.
Come here!
Wash all these clothes
and learn your lesson.
Isn't there a washing machine?
That thing wastes water
and electricity.
Besides, hand-washing is cleaner.
I only dirtied my own clothes.
Can I just wash mine?
I only have one mouth too.
Can I
just cook for myself?
Your dad only has one mouth too.
Can he just earn money
for himself?
After you've washed the clothes,
wash these mustard greens too.
Wash them and hang them up to dry,
got it?
That's too much.
Xin,
what did you scout out?
Let me see.
Oh my goodness.
Is she going to wash
a whole class's clothes?
Mrs. Huo calls this
punishing everyone fairly,
with no favorites.
Xin,
you need to help her.
Sweetie.
I heard from Cao Xin
that you have a book
that foreigners use
to tell fortunes with stars.
Can you lend it to me?
I won't take it for free.
I'll trade you something for it.
What will you trade?
Come,
you'll know when you come.
Bring your clothes.
Come.
Look.
It's the latest model.
Even your mom
can't wash clothes as well as it does.
You just have to
press a couple of buttons,
and you want to trade it for my book?
Take all these pickles.
There's plenty.
Deal.
Okay.
I'll go get the stuff for you.
Your mom said
you're not allowed to
visit our house whenever you want.
You're disobeying her behind her back.
If you don't tell on me,
it doesn't count as disobeying her.
Drink less of that stuff.
It's useless.
Intelligence is innate.
Look at me.
I don't drink anything
and still get good grades.
Be careful not to mess up.
Don't worry.
That's impossible.
Stop the car!
Stop!
Cao Xin.
Mrs. Huo.
You haven't had breakfast yet?
Here.
They've just been made.
They're filled with mustard greens.
No, thanks.
Take it.
Here are two more.
I'll put them in your backpack.
That's enough.
No way.
You are still growing.
Two aren't enough.
They're enough.
Alright.
Hurry up and go to school.
Go.
Thank you, Mrs. Huo.
Don't mention it.
Leave the lunchbox
in my yard tonight.
Okay.
I'm leaving.
Uncle Qi.
Going to school?
Did you see that?
No matter how far he is from home,
a son always remembers
his mother's cooking.
Honey,
what am I having for lunch?
Who cares? Eat whatever you want.
Alright, let's go.
Then buy me a pack of instant noodles.
Okay.
Besides tomatoes, see what else you want.
Towels are three yuan each.
Okay,
I'll take four.
Four towels?
Ten yuan.
Twelve. Twelve.
I'm buying so many at once.
Ten yuan. Ten yuan.
One of each color.
I can't do ten yuan.
I really can't.
I can't.
It's a small business.
Then I don't want them.
Don't... Don't go.
I'll give you a free bar of soap.
This soap is worth two yuan.
Four towels and a bar of soap
for twelve yuan.
Alright, alright, alright.
Okay?
This small business
really doesn't make much,
you know?
Okay.
Take care.
Making this little money
is really hard.
If you ask me,
no matter what you sell here,
you can't get a good price.
In the provincial capital,
a towel
can sell for dozens of yuan.
Dozens of yuan is nothing.
Shanghai is even crazier.
My daughter bought me a handkerchief
for one hundred and twenty yuan.
More precious than gold.
You're talking nonsense.
How could a handkerchief
cost one hundred and twenty?
I'm not talking nonsense.
I'll show you.
Look, doesn't it say
one hundred and twenty?
See? There's the tag.
I couldn't bear to take it off.
Really.
It's very precious.
Then you wouldn't dare use it.
Just display it at home.
Put it away quickly.
Yeah, I need to keep it safe.
Ma'am, you haven't paid yet.
How much is it?
Three yuan and ten cents.
Just give me three yuan.
Alright.
Come on, get on.
What if
we move to the provincial capital too?
The provincial capital?
I haven't even figured out Qingwu yet.
If we really
went to the provincial capital,
I'd be sold
and still help them count the money.
You know yourself pretty well.
Are you saying
we're going to spend our whole lives
staying here in Qingwu,
running a street stall?
What's wrong with running a street stall
in Qingwu for the rest of our lives?
Look,
these past few years,
even though it's been hard,
we've managed to
raise the kids.
When the time comes,
when one gets into college
and the other makes the national team,
our burden
will be completely lifted.
When that time comes,
why bother struggling?
That's why I say
you're short-sighted
and thick-headed.
You only see what's right in front of you.
Do you know how much
a year of college tuition is?
And when Qi Zhi
gets married and buys a house,
won't that all cost money?
As the saying goes,
a tree dies if moved,
but a person thrives.
The provincial capital is so big,
there must be more opportunities.
Right?
If you don't go out and try,
how will you know
if you can make it?
Besides,
living here in Qingwu
isn't exactly pleasant, is it?
We see the Cao family
every time we turn around.
Let's just move somewhere else.
It'll be quieter.
What do you think?
You're not discussing this with me.
You're giving me an ultimatum.
What did you say?
I mean,
my wife makes a good point.
My wife is far-sighted
and thinks ahead.
This family really can't do without you.
Then it's settled.
Do you still want this tape recorder?
Of course.
It would be a pity to throw it away.
But you guys never listen to it.
It's just sitting on the cabinet.
I listen to it.
Dad.
What happened to our house?
Did we get robbed?
With the state of our house,
if a thief really broke in,
they might be the unlucky ones.
We are moving.
I'll clean out
all this junk.
Sell what we can, and throw away the rest.
Move? Where are we moving to?
The provincial capital, Haizhou.
To be closer to you.
So you don't have to travel
back and forth on weekends.
How about it?
Surprised? Didn't see that coming?
Not surprised,
but I didn't see it coming.
Move this box
over here for me.
Mom.
Our family has lived in Qingwu
since your grandfather's generation
for fifty or sixty years.
We can't just move like that.
Yeah.
Your grandfather and your father
were both miners.
They stayed here
to help build the country.
We haven't worked in the mine
for a long time.
Why are we still staying here?
It's time to move.
Zhi.
They say the provincial capital
is dozens of times bigger than Qingwu.
It takes hours to drive
from one end to the other.
There's also an amusement park
and a Ferris wheel.
Have you ever been on a roller coaster?
I'm going out for some fresh air.
Where are you going? It's time to eat.
I'm not eating.
Aren't you going to pack?
Dad, look at him.
He hides whenever there's work
and slacks off.
He's trained all day
and then run all the way back.
He's probably tired.
After his usual training,
doesn't he run back too?
And doesn't he still have the energy
to go roller-skating
with his classmates at night?
He doesn't look tired to me.
Son, don't scare me.
Where exactly does it hurt?
Is it here?
Be gentle.
-My stomach hurts.
-What have you done to yourself?
What did you eat?
Stop twisting around.
Come on, son.
Get up and drink some water.
Drink some hot water.
Why are you
throwing up water?
What are we going to do?
What should we do?
How about we go to
a big hospital in the provincial capital?
You're about to compete
in the national team trials.
At this critical moment,
nothing else can go wrong.
Alright, get up.
We're going to the big hospital.
Let's go. Dad will carry you.
Let's go. Come on, get up.
-Hold on.
-Dad, don't touch me.
When you touch me,
my stomach churns
and hurts even more.
You...
I can't take it anymore.
Let's call an ambulance.
Here he is.
Qi Zhi.
Drink it.
You'll be fine after drinking it.
What is this?
Don't spill it.
Medicine.
Magic medicine.
He can't drink it.
Who knows what the Caos
are up to?
Look at you.
What am I up to?
A selfless heart, a devoted heart,
and a heart full of love.
You...
Otherwise,
I'll drink some.
Okay?
Look at you.
Let him try it.
Didn't he drink
Doctor Cao's medicine when he was a kid?
How can you take medicine blindly?
Who will take responsibility
if it makes him worse?
We have nothing to lose by trying.
How do you feel?
Dad.
Mom.
I have to say,
I feel much better after drinking it.
Thank you, Grandpa Cao.
Much better?
An instant cure.
Then...
What disease does Qi Zhi have?
Well, Qi Zhi.
Aihua.
I think I just heard someone say
that I had bad intentions.
Did you hear that?
Qinglian is just worried.
Please bear with her.
Look at you.
What are you mumbling about?
Speak up. I can't hear you.
I mean, sir,
I'm sorry.
It's our fault.
Look.
Aihua is a reasonable man.
Qinglian.
Is he saying he's sorry to me?
Qi Zhi's illness
is caused by spleen deficiency.
What does traditional Chinese medicine say?
In traditional Chinese medicine,
the spleen and stomach are
the foundation of acquired constitution.
If they are weak,
three turbidities can arise.
Over time.
Guess what?
The abdominal pain becomes unbearable.
Then... then how do we treat it?